Guide to the Congress of Clubs and Clubwomen of Western Pennsylvania Records, 1890-1963 AIS.1964.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Congress of Clubs and Clubwomen of Western Pennsylvania Records
1890-1963
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Congress of Clubs and Club Women of Western Pennsylvania
AIS.1964.10
50 Linear Feet (39 boxes)
Originating in 1890, the Congress of Clubs and Clubwomen of Western Pennsylvania was a women's organization that existed through 1963. The collection contains material about their departments, committees, divisions and schools that were in place to create a well rounded individual able to assimilate well in society. Included in the collection are the constitution and by-laws, membership lists, reports of departments and committees, minute books, correspondence, event programs, publications, and scrapbooks.
History
Originating in 1890, the Congress of Clubs and Clubwomen of Western Pennsylvania was a women's organization that existed through 1963. The object of the organization was to "foster a spirit of fraternalism among women and women's clubs; to compare methods of study and work; to create a higher public spirit; to promote a better social order; and to maintain an organized center for women's work". The Congress had two classes of membership: club and individual (adult and junior). A clubhouse was built in 1923 at 408 Penn Avenue. At this time, the organization represented 121 clubs and had a membership of over 12,000 women. This number grew to a membership of 47,000 women from 622 clubs in 1940.
The Congress of Clubs was divided into four different sections, namely: departments, committees, divisions and schools. Within these four sections were subcategories of, drama, education, evening, legislative and music. These sections and their subcategories existed throughout the entire life of the organization and were created for the betterment of the club, to provide entertainment for the club, to educate women of the community and make them more well rounded, or to provide charity for groups outside of the club.
The Drama Department provided the opportunity for women to participate in dramatic productions and also hired professional actors to perform for the club. The Education Department worked to provide educational programs for club members, but also funded several scholarships. The Evening Department was designed for working women who were not able to attend meetings during the work weekday. The Legislation Department dealt with national, state, and local legislation. The fact that the Congress of Clubs, especially in its infancy, regarded women's rights in politics as very important is reflected in this department. The Music Department provided the opportunity for women to participate in the Congress Choral, and the Musicale.
Scope and Content Notes
Each series is further described in a scope note following the beginning of the series in the contents list. The notes give date spans and explain the arrangement of materials within the series.
The collection is well rounded and includes historical items, meeting minutes, reports of departments and committees, financial records, publications, correspondence, event programs, and membership lists. However, the majority of the materials are in Series IV: Departments, Committees, Divisions, and Schools and Series IX: Correspondence.
Arrangement
This collection spans the years 1890 through 1963 and has been arranged according to ten series. Each series is further described in a scope note following the beginning of the series in the contents list. The notes give date spans and explain the arrangement of materials within the series.
Series I. Constitution and By-Laws
Series II. Annual and Quarterly Meetings
Series III. Board Meetings
Series IV. Departments, Committees, Divisions, and Schools
Series V. Affiliated Clubs
Series VI. Congress Juniors Division
Series VII. Clubhouse Business
Series VIII. Publications
Series IX. Correspondence
Series X. Scrapbooks
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mrs. Alice Phillips, February 3, 1964.
Previous Citation
Congress of Clubs and Clubwomen of Western Pennsylvania Records, 1890-1963, AIS.1964.10, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Women -- Pennsylvania -- Societies and clubs; Societies; Associations; Women; American Red Cross. Pittsburgh Area Chapter. Allegheny County Auxiliary No.1; Congress of Clubs and Club Women of Western Pennsylvania
- Constitution and By-Laws, 1890-1957; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  Throughout the existence of the Congress of Clubs and Clubwomen of Western Pennsylvania, the clubwomen continually revised and amended the constitution and by-laws of the organization. The eight folders in this series contain the original by-laws and constitution, correspondence, amendments and revised versions of the by-laws.
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1890-1957 (Box 1, Folder 1-8)
- Annual and Quarterly Meetings, 1915-1957; II.
  The minute books, titled Quarterly Meeting Records, include the minutes from both the Annual and Quarterly Meetings as well as any special meetings that were called. The series also contains information on planning the meetings and includes correspondence, programs, invitations, election information, and reports relating to these Annual and Quarterly Meetings. The dates on these documents range from 1921-1962.
  - Minutes, 1921-1956 (Box 1, Folder 9-15)
  - Correspondence and Notes, 1921-1934 (Box 1, Folder 16-26)
  - Correspondence and Notes, 1934-1945 (Box 2, Folder 1-30)
  - Correspondence and Notes, 1946-1962 (Box 3, Folder 1-37)
- Board Meetings, 1920-1959; III.
  Box 4 and the first 4 folders of Box 5 contain the minutes of the Board of Directors of the Congress of Clubs and Clubwomen of Western Pennsylvania. The remainder of Box 5 and the first 27 folders in Box 6 contain correspondence regarding the Board Meetings. The last five folders in Box 6 include minutes and correspondence of the Ex-Board, a group consisting of women who formerly served on the Board.
  - Minutes, 1920-1944 (Box 4, Folder 1-9)
  - Minutes, 1944-1957 (Box 5, Folder 1-4)
  - Correspondence and Notes, 1921-1944 (Box 5, Folder 5-18)
  - Board Meeting Correspondence, 1945-1957 (Box 6, Folder 1-27)
  - Ex-Board, 1944-1959 (Box 6, Folder 28-32)
- Departments, Committees, Divisions, and Schools, 1919-1957; IV.
  Boxes 7-14 contain material about departments, committees, divisions and schools. The folders for most of the departments, committees, divisions, and schools contain membership lists, minute books, correspondence, and notes. Departments of particular interest include Drama, Education, Evening, Legislation, and Music. The Drama Department includes records pertaining to drama productions as well as the hiring and promoting of professional actors to perform for the club. The Education Department contains records on educational programs and scholarships. Information is available on memorial scholarships, scholarships based on need, and their most long standing scholarship, which provided tuition for a female medical student. The Legislation Department regarded women's rights in politics as very important, which is reflected in these records. The Music Department includes records on the Congress Choral, and the Musicale. It also contains two folders of musical scores, circa 1925-1926. In addition to the typical records held by the many departments and committees, the Membership Committee records include New Member Lists, information on Membership Drives, Courtesy Members, Delinquent Members, and Life Members. The records of this committee also consist of correspondence regarding dues and resignations from the clubs, most significantly during the Depression. These resignations quite often include the reasons the members resigned from the club.
  - Departments, 1925-1958; 1.
    - Department Lists and Records, 1934-1941 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
    - Drama Department, 1930-1944 (Box 7, Folder 4-10)
    - Education Department, 1925-1958 (Box 7, Folder 11-31)
    - Evening Department, 1929-1934 (Box 7, Folder 32-36)
    - Fine Arts Department, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Home Department, 1929-1939 (Box 8, Folder 2-7)
    - Legislation Department, 1929-1951 (Box 8, Folder 8-15)
    - Literature Department, 1929-1938 (Box 8, Folder 16-20)
    - Music Department, 1925-1953 (Box 8, Folder 21-31)
    - Public Welfare Department, 1929-1931 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Recreation Department, 1927-1931 (Box 8, Folder 33-36)
    - Department of Ways and Means, 1929-1931 (Box 8, Folder 37-38)
    - Welfare Department, 1931-1935 (Box 8, Folder 39-41)
  - Committees, 1919-1957; 2.
    - Committee Membership Lists, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Advisory Committee, 1924-1956 (Box 9, Folder 2-4)
    - Affiliated Club Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Budget Committee, 1933-1958 (Box 9, Folder 6-11)
    - Civic Committee, 1920-1921 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Club Relations Committee, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Conservation Committee, 1920-1921 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Dramatic Committee, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Fair Price Committee, 1920-1921 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Finance Committee, 1908-1957 (Box 9, Folder 17-36)
    - Finance Committee, 1919-1952 (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
    - House Committee, 1922-1956 (Box 10, Folder 5-12)
    - Housekeepers Club, 1920-1921 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - International Relations Committee, 1933-1935 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Legislation Committee, 1934-1939 (Box 10, Folder 15-16)
    - Membership Committee, 1920-1955 (Box 10, Folder 17-45)
    - Membership Committee, 1920-1955 (Box 11, Folder 1-43)
    - Membership Committee, 1929-1947 (Box 12, Folder 1-34)
    - Membership Committee, 1949-1962 (Box 13, Folder 1-24)
    - Nominating Committee, 1923-1954 (Box 13, Folder 25-36)
    - Program Committee, 1925-1949 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Social Committee, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 38-39)
    - Social Hospitality Committee, 1933-1954 (Box 13, Folder 40-47)
    - Social Services Committee, 1920 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Study Committee, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Thrift Committee, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Ways and Means Committee, 1955-1957 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
    - Women's Action Committee, 1944-1947 (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
  - Divisions and Schools, 1920-1953; 3.
    - Bowling League, 1933-1953 (Box 14, Folder 7-11)
    - Business Women's Division (Box 14, Folder 12-16)
    - Current Events, 1929-1941 (Box 14, Folder 17-20)
    - Interest Groups "A","B","C", 1931-1933 (Box 14, Folder 21-24)
    - Magazine Review Class, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Parliamentary Law Class, 1936-1944 (Box 14, Folder 26-31)
    - Post-Gazette's Cooking School, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 32-33)
    - Recreation Class, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Speaker's Bureau, 1931-1961 (Box 14, Folder 35-39)
    - Speech Class, 1931-1932 (Box 14, Folder 40-41)
    - School of Physical Education, 1931-1940 (Box 14, Folder 42-51)
- Affiliated Clubs, 1925-1962; V.
  Makes up boxes 15-17 and box 18, folders 1-8 and supplies information on affiliated clubs. These records contain club applications, surveys, and correspondence for the years 1925 to 1962.
  - Club Application Blanks, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Club Applications, 1925-1949 (Box 15, Folder 2-19)
  - Correspondence, 1929-1940 (Box 15, Folder 20-39)
  - Correspondence, 1934-1960 (Box 16, Folder 1-30)
  - Correspondence Regarding Delegates from Affiliated Clubs, 1930-1931 (Box 16, Folder 31-32)
  - Correspondence Regarding Delegates from Affiliated Clubs, 1930-1935 (Box 17, Folder 1-7)
  - Questionnaires, undated (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
  - Replies to Questionnaires, 1927-1934 (Box 17, Folder 10-18)
  - Affiliated Club Records, 1930-1938 (Box 17, Folder 19-20)
  - Rental Contracts, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Club Resignations, 1930-1949 (Box 17, Folder 22-29)
  - Club Surveys, 1950-1955 (Box 17, Folder 30-36)
  - Club Surveys, 1956-1962 (Box 18, Folder 1-8)
- Congress Juniors Division, 1934-1961; VI.
  Folders 9-32 of box 18 consist of the by-laws, minutes and correspondence relating to the Congress Juniors Division during the years 1934-1961.
  - By Laws, 1934-1935 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1934-1948 (Box 18, Folder 10-11)
  - Correspondence, 1934-1961 (Box 18, Folder 12-32)
- Clubhouse Business, 1921-1953; VII.
  Boxes 19 and 20 contain mainly financial papers regarding the building and maintenance of the Clubhouse. The majority of these records are from 1921 to 1937. Clubhouse photographs from 1921 can be found in box 19, folders 3-4.
  - Building Fund Team Book, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
  - Clubhouse Photographs, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 3-4)
  - Campaigns for Building, 1921-1939 (Box 19, Folder 5-14)
  - Mortgage Club, 1931-1939 (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
  - Mortgage Plan, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 17-25)
  - Mortgage Fund, 1942-1943 (Box 19, Folder 26-31)
  - Mortgage Fund, 1942-1943 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
  - Accounts Past Due, 1934-1938 (Box 20, Folder 3-6)
  - Correspondence Regarding the Condemnation of Building, 1950-1953 (Box 20, Folder 7-9)
  - Financial Statements, 1927-1928 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Audit, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Applications for Positions in the Clubhouse, 1932,1937-1938 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Application for Manager of Clubhouse, 1933-1934 (Box 20, Folder 13-14)
  - Correspondence with Grace Spencer for Manager, 1934-1935 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Insurance Claims, 1925-1936 (Box 20, Folder 16-19)
  - Payroll Letters, 1937-1938 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Time Sheets, undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Heating Contracts, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Outside Work Estimates, 1922 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Printing Bids, 1933-1936 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Repair Work and Services, 1933-1934 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Estimates Submitted, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Receipts, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Tax Exemptions, 1922-1937 (Box 20, Folder 28-29)
  - Information on Taxes, 1921-1937 (Box 20, Folder 30-33)
  - Victory Tax (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Publications, 1917-1957; VIII.
  Boxes 21-24 and the first 27 folders of box 25 consist of publications that span the dates of the collection. These include the Congress Annual, Congress Outlet, Congress Lantern, Congress Chatter, Monthly Calenders, Official Directories, Publicity Programs, and Radio Programs. This series also includes materials about the publications in each folder. The Congress Outlet was published monthly, the Congress Lantern weekly, while various newsletters were distributed in between.
  - Congress Annual, 1945-1952 (Box 20, Folder 35-43)
  - Congress Annual, 1953-1957 (Box 21, Folder 44-51)
  - Congress Chatter, 1951-1957 (Box 21, Folder 52-62)
  - Congress Lantern, 1937-1941 (Box 21, Folder 63-67)
  - Congress of Club News, undated (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Congress Outlet, 1921-1923 (Box 21, Folder 69-71)
  - Congress Outlet, 1924-1932 (Box 22, Folder 1-10)
  - Congress Outlet, 1922-1926 (Box 22, Folder 11-17)
  - Correspondence with Catherine Gregg, Publisher of the Congress Outlet, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Congress Outlet, 1928-1931 (Box 22, Folder 19-26)
  - Congress Outlet, 1932-1937 (Box 23, Folder 1-5)
  - Monthly Bulletin Notes, 1921-1922 (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
  - Monthly Calendars, 1921-1950 (Box 23, Folder 8-15)
  - Official Directories, 1917-1963 (Box 23, Folder 16-20)
  - Women's Club Life, 1940-1941 (Box 23, Folder 21-23)
  - Publicity, 1929-1933 (Box 23, Folder 24-34)
  - Publicity, 1933-1950 (Box 24, Folder 1-14)
  - Radio Programs, 1928-1950 (Box 24, Folder 15-22)
  - Resolutions, 1929-1939 (Box 24, Folder 23-27)
- Correspondence, 1920-1963; IX.
  The remainder of box 24 through box 36 consists of correspondence that has been divided into three subseries according to organizations, events, and miscellaneous. The correspondence of the first two subseries is arranged alphabetically by organization, subject or event and can include reports, programs, announcements, and financial material. The miscellaneous correspondence subseries is arranged chronologically from 1920 to 1963 and then further organized alphabetically by correspondent within the year span. Circular letters and notes from the recording secretary can be found in this group of correspondence. Membership cards for the years 1923-1938 are also located at the end of the miscellaneous subseries in box 36.
  - Organizations, 1921-1953; 1.
    - Allegheny Conference on Community Development, 1945-1947 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Allegheny County League of Women's Voters, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - American Bible Society, 1938-1939 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - American Legion, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - American Red Cross, 1927-1946 (Box 24, Folder 32-34)
    - American Society for Control of Cancer, 1944-1945 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Better Traffic Committee, 1929-1940 (Box 24, Folder 36-38)
    - C-E-Z Light Bulb Project, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Civic Club of Allegheny County, 1931-1933 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Civic Light Opera, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Cleaner Pittsburgh Committee, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Cooperative Speakers Service, 1937-1938 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Department of Justice, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Department of Public Health, 1940-1941 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1929-1953 (Box 25, Folder 9-11)
    - Kilbuck Theater, 1935-1941 (Box 25, Folder 12-19)
    - Lawrenceville Neighborhood House, 1927-1928 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Milk and Ice Association, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - National Committee on Cause and Cure for War, 1928-1929 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - National Committee on Household Employment, 1936-1938 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - National Grandmother's Club, Inc., 1938-1940 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - National Recovery Administration, 1933-1934 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - National War Labor, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Near East Relief, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Office of Public Administration, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - People's Bond Issue Association, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - People's Pittsburgh Trust Company, 1935-1941 (Box 25, Folder 30-32)
    - Pennsylvania Association for the Blind, 1929-1931 (Box 25, Folder 33-34)
    - PA Civil Service Association, 1929-1930 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Pennsylvania Federation, 1939-1940, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Pittsburgh Council of Adult Education, 1937-1939 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Pittsburgh Girls Conference, 1928-1929 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Press Projected Book Fund, 1948-1949 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Review of Reviews Campaign, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Salvation Army, undated (Box 25, Folder 42-43)
    - Smoke Abatement League, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - State Federation of Pennsylvania Women, 1928-1928 (Box 25, Folder 45-52)
    - Theater Guild, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - United Service Organization, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - U.S. Treasury, 1942-1944 (Box 25, Folder 55-56)
    - WE Care Clubs, undated (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Welfare Fund of Pittsburgh, 1928-1929 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Western Pennsylvania Safety Council, 1928-1935 (Box 25, Folder 59-63)
    - YMCA Pittsburgh Council, 1921-1922 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Events, 1928-1958; 2.
    - Mailings for Special Events, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Invitations, 1932-1933 (Box 26, Folder 2-6)
    - Stationary, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - General Activities, 1939-1940 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Administration Day, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
    - Affiliated Club Day, 1934-1941 (Box 26, Folder 11-12)
    - Birthday Parties, 1939-1941 (Box 26, Folder 13-15)
    - Board Card Parties, 1932-52 (Box 26, Folder 16-35)
    - Board Card Parties, 1953-1954 (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
    - Boat Rides, 1931-1933 (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
    - Concerts, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Concert Series, 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 7-10)
    - Congress Chain Parties, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Contract Bridge Parties, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Cornelia Otis Skinner, 1930 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - "CYN" Budget Performance, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Duplicate Bridge Tournament, 1934-1937 (Box 27, Folder 15-16)
    - Flood Correspondence, 1936-1939 (Box 27, Folder 17-18)
    - Kirmess, 1928-1929 (Box 27, Folder 19-20)
    - Lecture Series, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 21-22)
    - Marathon Round Table, undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Memorial, 1928 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Open House Week, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Pennsylvania Week, 1947-1952 (Box 27, Folder 26-28)
    - Pop Concert, 1935-1937 (Box 27, Folder 29-30)
    - President's Luncheon, 1930-1934 (Box 27, Folder 31-32)
    - Programs, General, undated (Box 27, Folder 33-34)
    - Programs, 1928-1946 (Box 27, Folder 35-42)
    - Rent Contracts for Programs, 1945-1946 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Prospectives, 1929-1958 (Box 27, Folder 47-49)
    - Rummage Sale, 1933-1955 (Box 28, Folder 1-6)
    - Summer Activities, 1937-1957 (Box 28, Folder 7-11)
    - Summer Parties, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Theater Benefit, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Victory Booth at Gumbel's, 1942-1944 (Box 28, Folder 14-16)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1920-1963; 3.
    - 1920 (Box 28, Folder 17-20)
    - 1921 (Box 28, Folder 21-43)
    - 1922 (Box 28, Folder 44-47)
    - 1924 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 29, Folder 2-23)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 29, Folder 24-26)
    - 1928 (Box 29, Folder 27-52)
    - 1928 (Box 30, Folder 1-25)
    - 1929 (Box 30, Folder 26-50)
    - 1929 (Box 31, Folder 1-7)
    - 1930 (Box 31, Folder 8-15)
    - 1931 (Box 31, Folder 16-40)
    - 1932 (Box 31, Folder 41-49)
    - 1933 (Box 32, Folder 1-20)
    - 1934 (Box 32, Folder 21-35)
    - 1935 (Box 32, Folder 36-48)
    - 1936 (Box 32, Folder 49-51)
    - 1937 (Box 32, Folder 52-54)
    - 1937 (Box 33, Folder 1-11)
    - 1938 (Box 33, Folder 12-20)
    - 1939 (Box 33, Folder 21-28)
    - 1940 (Box 33, Folder 29-34)
    - 1941 (Box 33, Folder 35-38)
    - 1942 (Box 33, Folder 39-43)
    - 1943 (Box 33, Folder 44-46)
    - 1943 (Box 34, Folder 1-9)
    - 1944 (Box 34, Folder 10-13)
    - 1945 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - 1946 (Box 34, Folder 15-16)
    - 1947 (Box 34, Folder 17-22)
    - 1948 (Box 34, Folder 23-26)
    - 1949 (Box 34, Folder 27-29)
    - 1950 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - 1951 (Box 34, Folder 29-39)
    - 1952 (Box 34, Folder 40-41)
    - 1953 (Box 34, Folder 42-51)
    - 1954 (Box 35, Folder 1-4)
    - 1955 (Box 35, Folder 5-17)
    - 1956 (Box 35, Folder 18-21)
    - 1957 (Box 35, Folder 22-30)
    - 1963 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Membership Cards (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Membership Cards (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Scrapbooks, 1921-1960; X.
  Boxes 37-39 consist of scrapbooks for the majority of the years between 1921 and 1960. The scrapbooks primarily contain newspaper clippings with some event programs.
  - 1921-1943,1944 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - 1948-1949, 1954-1955 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - 1955-1956, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 1)